

CONTACT

- +(40) 755 934 953
- ✓ ancamatei2012@gmail.com
- P Cluj-Napoca, Cluj, Romania
- in linkedin.com/in/anca-m-matei/

LANGUAGES

- Romanian (Native)
- English (Fluent)
- French (Intermediate)

SKILLS

- O HTML5
- CSS (with SASS)
- JavaScript
- React
- Angular
- Git (Github)
- Responsive Web Design
- Rapid Learning

EDUCATION

2009-2015

UNIVERSITY OF MEDICINE 'IULIU HATIEGANU' CLUJ-NAPOCA Bachelor of Medicine

2013-2014

UNIVERSITÉ GRENOBLE ALPES Erasmus exchange

2005-2009

COLEGIUL NATIONAL 'B.P.HASDEU' BUZAU

Mathematics and Informatics - High School Diploma

ANCA-MARIA MATEI

Junior Frontend Web Developer

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a JavaScript developer, currently specializing in the React frontend library, with a focus on responsive design.

Due to my background in medicine, I bring discipline, continuous skill development and adaptability to diverse team environments.

I am enthusiastic about joining a team where I can collaborate and benefit from mentorship opportunities to further learn and grow.

WORK EXPERIENCE

RESIDENT DOCTOR IN DIABETES 2020 - NOW

County Emergency Clinical Hospital - Cluj-Napoca

ENDOCRINOLOGIST | 2020 - 2022

Omnimedical Clinic - Cluj-Napoca

RESIDENT DOCTOR IN ENDOCRINOLOGY | 2016 - 2019

County Emergency Clinical Hospital - Cluj-Napoca

PROJECTS

Portfolio Site

ancamatei.netlify.app

GitHub Projects

github.com/Anca2022

EuroTour Car Rental - Angular

euro-tour.ro

Recipe App - React

recipe-app-0b1.netlify.app

Kindergarden Website

kinder-g.netlify.app

Food Mine - Angular

foodmine-y.netlify.app